cwonder.com 2014-06-25

# C. Wonder

  **CWonder.com Privacy Policy**

Welcome to CWonder.com (the “Site”), which is owned and operated by C. Wonder, LLC (“C. Wonder” “we” or “us”). As a customer of C. Wonder, your trust is our most important asset. This Privacy Policy applies to the personal information we collect from you when you register for a Site account, place an order with us, subscribe to CWonder.com E-mail Updates (our e-mail newsletter), or otherwise send a request or inquiry to us.  This Privacy Policy describes:

The types of information we collect from you, 

How we use, share and protect this information, and 

The choices you can make about your information.

<<<<This policy is subject to the provisions of our Terms and Conditions of Use, which are incorporated by reference into this policy. If you do not agree with any aspect of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site.>>>>

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy by posting such changes or updates to the Site. Amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted.  It is your responsibility to review any such changes or updates and check the Website from time to time to be sure you understand all terms and conditions, agreements and policies of the Website and are in compliance with them. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the last modified date that appears at the end of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance of the amended Privacy Policy. 

**Categories of Personal Information We Collect**

We collect personal information from you when you register for a Site account, place an order with us, subscribe to CWonder.com E-mail Updates (our e-mail newsletter), or otherwise send a request or inquiry to us. In general, the types of personal information we collect include:

·         Registration Information: When you register with us, we may collect your name, shipping and billing address, e-mail, phone number and other contact information.

·         Order History: When you make purchases with us, we collect and store information about your purchases, such as order date, order amount, items purchased, payment method, shipping information, and the like.

·         Purchase Information: If you make a purchase through the Site, we collect your shipping and payment information, such as you credit or debit card number, expiration date and other information necessary to process your payment. We use this information only to process your purchase. We do not store this information unless you are a registered user and you choose to save this information to your account for future purchases.

·         Site Activities: We and our third party partners use cookies and other tracking technologies to automatically collect information about you when you visit our Site or use our services, including IP address, browser type, operating system, date and time of visit, time spent on and/or logged on to Site, pages visited, links clicked, items viewed, items added to your shopping cart, referring URL, social media username and other Site activity. We may combine such site information with the personal information we have collected from you. For more information, see the “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies” section, below.

·         Other Information: We also collect and store information about any inquiries or communications you submit to us, and any promotions in which you participate at our Site. In addition, we collect your e-mail address and name if you sign up to receive information about the latest deals, promotions and information from C. Wonder. In addition, we may receive other aggregate, demographic information about our customers.

·         We may also collect personal information about you from other third parties, such as demographic firms, to make our future service and marketing efforts more efficient and personalized for you.

**  How We Use Your Information **

In general, we use the information we collect from you, including any personal information, for the following purposes:

  * To process and fulfill your order, including to send you e-mails to confirm your order status and shipment, or to otherwise communicate with you about your order;
  * To communicate with you about your account;
  * If you have opted in, to send you marketing information by e-mail, postal mail and/or text message, about our products, services, contests, and promotions;
  * To help us learn more about your shopping preferences, to develop and provide products and services tailored to your interests and to otherwise personalize your experiences at our Site;
  * To better understand how users access and use our Site on an aggregate level;
  * To facilitate social shopping experiences through major social media platforms;
  * To provide troubleshooting, technical support and customer service to users;
  * To help us address problems with and improve our Site design, products and services;
  * To enhance your shopping experience;
  * To analyze trends and statistics and for research purposes;
  * To protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business; and
  * To investigate, prevent or take action regarding violations of this Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions of Use.

 How We Disclose Your Personal Information 

We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes, and we will not do so unless we first seek, and receive, your consent.  However, we may disclose your personal information under the following circumstances: 

•               C. Wonder Affiliates: We may share your personal information with other members of the C. Wonder family of companies (e.g. C. Wonder affiliates and subsidiaries). When we do, they may only use personal information for the purposes described in this policy.

•               Providers of Services to C. Wonder: We may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents that perform functions on our behalf (such as a printer, e-mail, mobile marketing, analytics providers, call center service providers, sweepstakes vendors, payment processors, data enhancement, or fraud prevention providers) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These third parties have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of personal information and to only use it for the purposes for which they have been engaged by us. If using PayPal services for purchases please refer to PayPal’s User Agreement and Privacy Policy for additional information https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/legalhub-full?country.x=US&locale.x=en_US. 

•               Business Transfers: If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the acquiring company.

•               Legal Process: We may disclose the information we collect from you in order  to comply with the law, a judicial or administrative proceeding, court order, subpoena or other legal process.

•               To Protect Us and Others: We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety, rights or property of any person or party, or violations of our Terms and Conditions of Use or this Privacy Policy.

•               Notwithstanding the above, we may share aggregate or de-identified information about users with other third parties for marketing, advertising, research or other purposes. For example, if we display advertisements on behalf of a third party, we may share aggregate, demographic information with that third party about the users to whom we displayed the advertisements.

**  Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

When you interact with the Site, we strive to make your experience easy and meaningful. We may use or engage others to use cookies, clear gifs and Flash LSOs to track user activity and collect Site data. We may combine this information with other personal information we have collected from you, and may use this combined information for future marketing initiatives and to help us improve our website presentation and your overall shopping experience.

Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. There are two types of cookies: session-based and persistent-based cookies.

•               Session Cookies: Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you during a session or while you are logged in to the Site. This allows us to process your online transactions and requests, store the items you have added to your shopping cart, and verify your identity after you have logged in and as you move through our Site.

•               Persistent Cookies: Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. We use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity, which may be combined with other user information.

Third Party Cookies. In addition, we may permit certain third party cookies to be placed on our Site. For example, we may engage third parties to track and analyze non-personally identifiable Site data. We use the data collected by such third parties to help us administer and improve the quality of the Site and services and to analyze usage. We do not provide these third parties with any personal information that we have collected about you.

We may also work with select partners to distribute web advertisements based on our customers’ internet browsing patterns. We do not provide these third parties with personal information. You may opt out of many of these ad networks, at any time, by going here: http://www.networkadvertising.org and following the instructions to opt-out. We do not have access to or control over these third party cookies nor does this Privacy Policy cover such third parties’ collection and use of data.

Disabling Cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Site visitors who disable their web browsers’ ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Site; however, many Site features, such as the shopping cart, will not function if you disable cookies.

Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs). We or the third parties we engage to track and analyze Site data may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) to help us better manage content on the Site. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages.

Flash Cookies. We may use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your Site preferences, to personalize your visit, or to display content based upon what you view on our Site. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. We do not have access to or control over these third party cookies nor does this Privacy Policy cover such third parties’ use of data.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount and type of data stored. In addition, you cannot control, delete, or disable the acceptance of Flash cookies through your browser. To learn how to manage your settings for Flash cookies, visit http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118.

California "Do Not Track" Disclosure.  We do not collect personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across third party websites or online services.  Our third party partners may combine personally identifiable information collected as described in this Privacy Policy with personally identifiable information collected over time and across third party websites or online services. For example, social networks such as Pinterest, Facebook or Twitter will collect information regarding items or purchases you choose to share through the Site. 

**Your Choices Regarding Marketing**

We use personal information that you provide to us to send you direct mail or e-mail advertisements for products or services that we or other companies that we work with offer and that we think you may be interested in.

If you do not want to receive these communications, you can update your marketing information-sharing preferences using the following methods:

• E-mail customercare@cwonder.com, or 

• Mail your request to:

                C. Wonder

                1115 Broadway

                New York, NY 10010

Please note your preference as stated below:

“I prefer not to receive e-mail advertisements, such as updates regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events.” (You may also click the designated link at the bottom of all CWonder.com e-mail advertisements to be removed from future e-mail updates.)

“I prefer not to receive direct mail advertisements, such as periodic catalogs and mailings regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events.” (Please note that direct mail requests may take up to six to eight weeks to become effective.)

**Links to Other Websites and Services**

Websites provided by C. Wonder may include links to other Internet sites maintained by third parties. C. Wonder provides these links to you solely as a convenience, and the inclusion of these links and associated sites does not imply endorsement by C. Wonder of the linked sites. You access these sites at your own risk and by accessing them you leave C. Wonder’s website. Linked sites are not under the control of C. Wonder and C. Wonder is not responsible for the contents of these sites.

**Children’s Privacy**

This Site is not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from, or target our Site to, children under the age of 13. If we become aware that any child under the age of 13 has submitted any personal information to C. Wonder through the Site, we will delete his or her information from our files. If you believe we have collected personal information about your child, you may contact us at customercare@cwonder.com and request that we remove it.

**Security**

We maintain commercially reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of personal information transmitted to us using this website. For example, to guard your information, our website uses SSL technology, which encrypts your credit card number, name and address so only C. Wonder is able to decode this information. To be sure your connection is secure, look at the bottom status bar of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser) the SSL is active and your information is secure. Most browsers offer additional security alerts as well. If for some reason you are unable to connect to our secure server, please email us at customercare@cwonder.com to place an order by email. You should be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security all of the time.

There are also certain steps you should take to safeguard your account and information. For example, you should select a secure password that only you know, and should always sign out of your account when finished. It is your responsibility to protect the confidentiality of your password in order to prevent unauthorized access to your account. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your account and password. You should immediately change your password and notify us if you discover or suspect any unauthorized use of your account.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to change this policy, and to apply any changes to information previously and subsequently collected, as permitted by law. If there are material changes to this policy, or if our information practices change materially with regard to personal information that we have previously collected from you, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on our website with a new effective date and/or notifying you by email, and will give you the choice of opting out of the material changes.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties for those third parties direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: customercare@cwonder.com. Please allow 30 days for a response.

Assignment

C. Wonder may freely assign this policy or any of its right and/or obligations hereunder.

**Protecting Your Personal Information**

You may come in contact with websites, e-mails or texts that try to lure you into providing personal information with the offer of a C. Wonder gift card. C. Wonder does not sponsor these offers nor are we affiliated with the promotion originators. If you become aware of any potentially fraudulent activity on a website or in an e-mail or text, please forward the information to customercare@cwonder.com so that we can follow up. We take these matters, and the protection of our customers’ sensitive information, very seriously.

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us at: 

C. Wonder

1115 Broadway

New York, NY

10010

Effective Date: [2/12/2014]
